George Boholteanu

Software Developer

I am a software developer with a strong passion for full-stack development. Drawing from my background in Architecture and Visualization, where I focused on delivering exceptional user experiences through ultra-realistic graphics/ CGIs. Excited to enhance my skills on back-end coding to create well-rounded, user-centric applications.

CONTACT (A)

London, UK | +447759311139

george.boholteanu@gmail.com

https://github.com/georgeboholteanu https://www.linkedin.com/in/georgeboholteanu-638957267/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Web Developer - PROFILETREE (Sep 2023 - Present)

- Conducted in-depth competitor analysis for a comprehensive career guidance app presenting findings to leadership.
- Wireframing landing page using Figma
- Web Designing using Wordpress to create landing page and a quizz application.

Front End Developer - EDX Trilogy (Nov 2022 - Mar 2023)

- Developed a series of web applications utilizing Agile methodologies.
- Proficient in HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, React and Node.js.
- Created a Freelancer Booking App, a Trivia App using Trivia API and GIPHY API, Personal Portfolio, and a Weather Dashboard using Openweather API.

Software Developer - Self Development (Mar 2020 - Present)

- Web design for a Fitness Club. Node-Sequelize Cloud Authentication App
- Designed and developed a Python-based Smart Assets Manager UI for data organization and web scraping.
- Conducted web scraping and data wrangling for Premier League match results using Python.
- Created animated data visualizations using Flourish App and developed UI tools in 3D Studio Max for automation.

Lead 3D Visualizer - Freelance (February 2020 - Present)

- Produced marketing CGIs for clients like HENLEY Real Estates Investments and WESTWAY Architects.
- Led client meetings, translated their vision into design proposals, and managed project timelines.

Architectural Visualizer - AHMM Architects (Apr 2017 - Pres)

- Established an efficient content management system, automating asset processes. Introduced a content library for streamlined design, alleviating repetitive tasks.
- Solved recurring visualization issues within the R&D team
- Delivered a variety of CGIs for design decision-making.
- Provided mentorship and guidance to junior visualizers.

3D Visualizer - Foster and Partners (Sept 2014 - Apr 2017)

- Collaborated with senior visualizers to produce outstanding CGIs for clients worldwide on high-profile projects.

SKILLS 🤹

- Programming: Python, React, JavaScript
- Web Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Figma, **Express**
- Version Control: Git
- Tools: 3D Studio Max, Photoshop, Illustrator
- Data Visualization: Flourish App
- Soft Skills: Problem-solving, creativity, adaptability, effective communication, collaboration, leadership, continuous learning, empathy.

EDUCATION A



EDX Trilogy

Front End Web Development Bootcamp** (Mar 2023)

SOLOLEARN COURSES

- Python for Data Science Course (Dec 2021)
- Python Intermediate Course (Dec 2021)
- SQL Course (Nov 2021)

Univ. of Architecture, Bucharest. Romania

Master in Architectural Design (Jul 2014)

INTERESTS

- Technology
- Sports
- Self Development